let quiz=[
    {
      question: "What is '?' in the given sequence -> 12*12=9, 23*23=16, 34*34=? :",
      option: [
           "11",
           "13",
           "15",
           "16",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Math Question Mark Brain Teaser , 1=4, 2=16, 3=64, 4=? :",
      option: [
           "238",
           "256",
           "252",
           "254",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What value will replace the question mark in the puzzle -> 1+3=34, 5+2=27, 5+1=16, 3+5=58, 2+4=?? :",
      option: [
           "64",
           "56",
           "46",
           "36",
      ],
       answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "90% of people fail to solve this math puzzle -> A-A-A=20, B-B-B=15, C-C-C=25, then A+B+C=?? :",
      option: [
           "45",
           "-20",
           "35",
           "-60",
      ],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Solve the value of D -> A+B=15, B*C=84, C/4=3, B+D=18 : ",
      option: [
           "4",
           "8",
           "12",
           "11",
      ],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "If 9=63, 8=48, 7=35, Then 4=? :",
      option: [
           "4",
           "8",
           "12",
           "16",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Solve this logical Math puzzle -> If 1+9+8=1, Then 2+8+9=? :",
      option: [
           "11",
           "3",
           "10",
           "1",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Solve this logical Math puzzle -> 11+11=4, 12+12=6, 13+13=8, 14+14=?? :",
      option: [
           "1",
           "0",
           "10",
           "5",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Break the logic behind the given mathematical puzzle -> 2/2=1, 6/5=3, 10/11=5, 16/19=?? :",
      option: [
           "7",
           "8",
           "11",
           "13",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Guess which number should be replaced by the '?' in the given series -> 0, 10, 1110, 3110, 132110, ? :",
      option: [
           "1113220111",
           "1211330111",
           "1113122110",
           "1131220312",
      ],
      answer: 3 ,
    },
    {
  question: "Three pencils cost the same as two erasers . Four erasers cost the same as one ruler . Pencils are more expensive than rulers. If the first two statements are true , the third statement is :",
  option: [
  "True",
  "False",
  "Uncertain",
  "Given Information is not sufficient ",
  ],
  answer: 2, 
},
{
  question: "Look Carefully for the pattern , and then choose which pairs of numbers come next ? 9 16 23 30 37 44 51 ",
  option: [
  "59 66",
  "56 62",
  "58 66",
  "58 65",
  ],
  answer: 4, 
},
{
  question: "Look at this series : U32 , V29 , ___ , X23 , Y20 , ... What number should fill the blank ?",
  option: [
  "W26",
  "W17",
  "Z17",
  "Z26",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
{
  question: "If both p and q are true then :",
  option: [
  "(p^q) is true",
  "~(p^q) is true ",
  "(~p)^q is true ",
  "p^(~q) is true",
  ],
  answer:1 , 
},
{
  question: "A line which cuts a pair of parallel lines is called :",
  option: [
  "Tangent",
  "Chord",
  "Transversal",
  "Intersector",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
    ]
    
